[
    {
        "question": "In the question below choose the option opposite in meaning to the word in capital letters:Chidi is naturally TACITURN",
        "optionA": "garrulous",
        "optionB": "cheerful",
        "optionC": "dumb",
        "optionD": "lively",
        "answer": "garrulous"
    },

    {
        "question": "In the question below choose the option opposite in meaning to the word in capital letters:To most people last Christmas was an AUSTERE period ",
        "optionA": "severe",
        "optionB": "sour",
        "optionC": "stern",
        "optionD": "prosperous",
        "answer": "prosperous"
    },

    {
        "question": "In the question below choose the option opposite in meaning to the word in capital letters: He is loved for his ALTRUISM.",
        "optionA": "benevolence",
        "optionB": "sincerity",
        "optionC": "kindness",
        "optionD": "selfishness",
        "answer": "selfishness"
    },

    {
        "question": "In the question below choose the option opposite in meaning to the word in capital letters. The chief was GENEROUS in his award of university scholarshipst",
        "optionA": "maive",
        "optionB": "reserved",
        "optionC": "happy",
        "optionD": "callous",
        "answer": "mean"
    },

    {
        "question": "In the question below choose the option opposite in meaning to the word in capital letters:The military Governor UPHELD the decision of his cabinet",
        "optionA": "held up",
        "optionB": "undercut",
        "optionC": "abolished",
        "optionD": "reversed",
        "answer": "abolished"
    },

    {
        "question": "Choose the option that best best completes the gap(s).Olu brought his clothes and those of his _________ ?",
        "optionA": "senior brother",
        "optionB": "elder brothers",
        "optionC": "elder brother's",
        "optionD": "Support",
        "answer": "elder brothers"
    },

    {
        "question": "Choose the option that best best completes the gap(s).I watched him as he _________ the hole?",
        "optionA": "digs",
        "optionB": "is digging",
        "optionC": "dugged",
        "optionD": "dug",
        "answer": "dug"
    },

    {
        "question": "Choose the option that best best completes the gap(s).The clubs were not _________ on a solid ethical base?",
        "optionA": "founded",
        "optionB": "created",
        "optionC": "funded",
        "optionD": "found",
        "answer": "founded"
    },

    {
        "question": "Choose the option that best best completes the gap(s).He wrote to you, _________?",
        "optionA": "hasn't he",
        "optionB": "wouldn't he",
        "optionC": "didn't he",
        "optionD": "hadn't he",
        "answer": "didn't he"
    },

    {
        "question": "In the question below choose the option opposite in meaning to the word in capital letters:The military Governor UPHELD the decision of his cabinet",
        "optionA": "held up",
        "optionB": "undercut",
        "optionC": "abolished",
        "optionD": "reversed",
        "answer": "abolished"
    },

    {
        "question": "In the question below choose the option opposite in meaning to the word in capital letters: The increase in transport fares DETERRED our club from planning an excursion this year.",
        "optionA": "encouraged",
        "optionB": "restricted",
        "optionC": "impelled",
        "optionD": "irritated",
        "answer": "encouraged"
    },

    {
        "question": "In the question below choose the option opposite in meaning to the word in capital letters:This card ENTITLES you to attend the film show",
        "optionA": "disqualifies",
        "optionB": "discourages",
        "optionC": "disenchants",
        "optionD": "proclaims",
        "answer": "disqualifies"
    },

    {
        "question": "Choose the option that best best completes the gap(s). Did you have _________ when you went to visit the medical doctor?",
        "optionA": "diarrhoea",
        "optionB": "diarrehea",
        "optionC": "diarhoea",
        "optionD": "diarhea",
        "answer": "diarrhoea"
    },

    {
        "question": "Choose the option that best best completes the gap(s).Your performance will improve if you _________ hard?",
        "optionA": "practise",
        "optionB": "are practising",
        "optionC": "practical",
        "optionD": "would practice",
        "answer": "practise"
    },

    {
        "question": "Choose the option that best best completes the gap(s).The brave hunter killed the _________ in the forest? ",
        "optionA": "big black spitting cobra",
        "optionB": "black big spitting cobra",
        "optionC": "big spitting cobra black",
        "optionD": "big spitting black cobra",
        "answer": "big black spitting cobra"
    }
]